♪ It seems today
that all you see ♪
♪ Is violence in movies
and sex on TV ♪
♪ But where are those
good old-fashioned values ♪
♪ On which we used to rely? ♪
♪ Lucky there's a family guy ♪
♪ Lucky there's a man
who positively can do ♪
♪ All the things that make us ♪
♪ Laugh and cry ♪
♪ He's... a...
Fam... ily... Guy! ♪
All right, see
you guys later.
Me and Brian are
going to play laser tag
with Joe and Quagmire.
What?! No, you're not.
Tonight's our family night.
We agreed that every Sunday,
we'd do something together.
(clears throat)
What?
Oh, nothing. I was just
clearing my throat.
Good. I thought you were
going to say something.
But, Lois, we
already made plans.
Yeah, I can't leave
those guys alone.
Last time they hung out
without me was a disaster.
All right, movie night.
I am so psyched
for Reindeer Games!
What, I thought we
were watching La Vie En Rose.
What do you mean,
Reindeer Games is great!
Everything goes wrong on the one
day it has to go right.
But La Vie En Rose
is a beautiful movie
about the real life tragedy
of Edith Piaf.
Usually Peter would
break the tie.
Well, Peter
isn't here, is he?!
Because you were
supposed to be watching him,
but you were smoking
marijuana and he drowned!
What? No, he's at
a PTA meeting.
Where the hell
did you get that story?
I don't know! I just can't stand
it when he's not here!
Peter, you've got
every other night of the week
to spend with your buddies.
This is the one night
we've set aside for our family.
Is that really
too much to ask?
(sighs)
I guess you're right.
Come on, Brian.
Come upstairs.
I wanna show you a freckle on my
sack that I'm concerned about.
It has irregular edges.
(window opening)
BRIAN (whispers): Peter,
what are you doing?
PETER (whispers):
I'm not goin' to Family Night.
My agreeing with Lois
was just pure theater.
Come on, we're
jumping off the roof.
Are you insane?!
We'll kill ourselves!
Don't worry, we can fly.
I got this pixie dust
from a magic fairy.
Either that or it's speed
I got from a transvestite
at a diner.
(snorting)
(yells): It's the speed!
It's the speed from the diner!
Peter, let go of me!
(yells)
Damn it!
So what are we gonna do
for Family Night?
Oh, would you shut up?
All the good people are gone.
Hey!
Welcome to Quahog Laser Tag.
Please pay attention
while I show y'all
how to put on y'all's vests.
Sir, can I use you
to demonstrate?
Thank you, I have
longed for your attention
since the moment I arrived.
Now, put this on
over your shoulders.
Good.
Now, I'm gonna need
you to squats down
like your underwears
is done for,
but you might still
save the jeans.
Now, you's gonna wanna latch the
front to the back like so...
Did everybody get that?
Boy, a lot of heat
comes off you, don't it?
(lasers zapping)
All right, keep an
eye out for Peter.
He's oddly competitive
at this stuff.
Yeah, and he seems to be weirdly
physically fit at this place.
Yeah, it's almost like he has
unrealistic abilities
when we play laser tag.
All right, well, if we just
stick together, then...
Zap! Zap! Zap!
What the...
No way!
How'd you learn
to do that?
The question isn't how I do it.
It's how I forgive myself
for what I've done.
(zap)
Yeah, winner!
Right here!
All right, pal,
what do I get?
Well, for five dollars,
you could get
your picture in a fake newspaper
with a humorous headline.
Wow, my picture
in the paper.
I didn't even
get that when
I brought that kitten
and gorilla together.
Huh?
Did I tell ya, Lois?
Oh, that's beautiful, Peter.
She's taking care of that
kitten like it's her own.
Yep, I knew eventually she'd
stop tearin' 'em in half.
There you two are!
We waited for you
for four hours!
Where the hell
have you been?!
Look, Lois,
I know you're mad,
but I think this will prove
that I did the right thing.
I put our family
on the map tonight.
No longer will we be
just those faceless nobodies
who brought the bird flu
to Quahog.
You know, there's something
seriously wrong with a man
who always puts
his friends over his family.
Come on, Lois, I think
you're overreacting.
What's so wrong about a guy
hanging out with his buddies?
Buddies?
You're one of his buddies?
Yeah. And you know why?
'Cause I don't try to tell him
what he can and can't do.
Oh, please, Brian.
You're just two people
who live in the same house.
If you didn't,
you'd never hang out
with each other
in a million years.
He owns you.
You're his property.
He used to hang you
in the garage
so his fender
wouldn't hit the wall.
(music playing over radio)
You're there.
You're there!
I couldn't hear you.
The radio was too loud.
I'm going to bed.
You know,
Lois is right, Brian.
You think you're Peter's pal,
but you're really not.
You're just his dog.
Well, that's where
you're wrong. Watch this.
Hey, Peter, you want
to go hit the Clam?
Nah, there's no way
she's in the mood.
Let's just go to the bar.
Sounds good.
Headin' to the bar
with my friend, Peter.
You're lying
to yourself, Brian.
Like those girls who insist
their best friends
are attractive.
Oh, Stewie, I can't wait for
you to meet my best friend.
She is so cute.
Yeah, she sounds awesome.
Oh, my God, yeah.
People ask her
if she's a model
all the time.
Here she comes!
(chuckles)
Okay, okay,
that was an extreme example,
but face it, ladies,
your best friends are not hot.
Uh, Peter, your seat belt
back here doesn't work right.
What's gonna happen to you
that hasn't already happened?
Peter, look out
for that car!
(high-pitched tone resonates)
That's not a car.
What is that?!
(all screaming)
Hello?
Anybody here?
Hey.
Do you work here?
I don't know.
Doesn't look like it.
Who are you?
I... I don't know.
I-I just woke up here.
I seem to be
a heavyset fellow.
You do.
Thank God someone
else is here.
You two seem to be the only
ones in this hospital.
No, I'm here, too.
Any of you guys
know what's going on?
I just woke up in
one of these rooms.
I have no idea
how I got here.
I don't even
know who I am.
All I know is,
I'm extremely important
because there are drawings of me
on all the bathroom doors.
See?
It's glued on there, too, so I'm
pretty sure it's permanent.
This is really weird.
We seem perfectly coherent,
it's just we can't
remember who we are.
It's like our identities
have been
wiped out somehow.
Maybe we can find somebody
to help us.
(dial tone droning)
The whole town seems
to be deserted.
Well, if there are
only four of us,
I propose we start a band.
And I propose we call
ourselves Robes of Teal.
Aw, damn it.
Well, we could still be a band
and choose a different name.
Oh, no, Robes of Teal
was the whole thing.
What the hell happened?
Where is everybody?
You don't suppose...
Do you think, we're the
only people on Earth?
I don't know.
I tell ya what,
I'm gonna open up
this bag of Chex Party Mix.
If people don't show up,
then we're it.
Yep, we're it.
All right, look, we know
we woke up in the hospital,
so maybe there was some kind
of catastrophe
that we were all spared.
Or maybe we were all
in some kind of accident.
Well, that would explain
why you're in a wheelchair.
You must have gotten hurt
worse than the rest of us.
Yeah, I got hit so hard,
it knocked my pee into a bag.
None of this
makes any sense.
Where the hell
is everybody?
Well, if we wait
till tax day,
I'm sure the tax man
will show up.
Ha. You should tweet that.
Okay.
(cell phone buzzes)
(laughs)
This guy's hilarious.
I'm gonna retweet this.
(both cell phones buzz)
Huh.
Mm.
Social media is bringing us
all closer together.
Unfollow.
Hey, you know,
if we're all gonna be
tryin' to figure
this out together,
maybe it would be easier
if we gave each other names.
That's a great idea.
Hey, maybe my name
is on this collar.
Cremate, don't bury.
Okay, that's a downer.
You know what?
I'm gettin' a feeling
about my name.
I think my name
might be Shirt Pants.
Shirt Pants?
What kind of name is that?
I don't know.
What's your name?
I kinda think
it's Manly Walker.
Wheeler?
No, Walker.
No, you're not hearing me right.
It's Walker.
It's probably Wheeler.
I sorta think
my name is Earl.
(My Name is Earl theme plays)
What was that?
I don't know.
Apparently, I made
some sort of reference.
Hey, check it out.
Looks like a bar.
(sighs) I could go
for a stiff one.
I think they got
a pill for that.
Shirt Pants!
Who else but Shirt Pants?
♪ He's Shirt Pants,
Shirt Pants ♪
♪ She's tryin' to remember,
but he really can't ♪
♪ He's Shirt Pants,
Shirt Pants ♪
♪ All I know for sure is I'm
wearing a shirt and pants. ♪
Hello?
♪ A-well-a everybody's heard
about the bird ♪
♪ B-B-Bird, bird, bird,
b-bird's the word... ♪
That's annoying.
BRIAN:
It just doesn't make sense
that there aren't any people.
This couldn't have
happened naturally.
Something must have
caused this, or someone.
Well, when I find that person,
I'm gonna strangle him.
I had a life,
and he took it away from me.
I don't remember it,
but I bet it was pretty good.
Yeah, me, too.
I bet I was a doctor
who had to deal with
a lot of serious stuff,
but always found a way
to keep things light.
Oh, my God,
she's beautiful.
Yeah, she is.
It's not yours.
Yours died.
Yeah, and I bet I answered
the customer complaint line
at a Danish cookie company.
Hello, Danish cookie company.
No, I know they don't
taste very good.
Well, because
they're very dry, aren't they?
I mean, t-they came in a tin,
how fresh did you think
they were gonna be?
Look, it's dark
and freezing in Denmark.
Everybody who made these cookies
has shot themselves.
Well, I bet I did something
really important and exciting.
Like-like maybe I was
a speechwriter
for the first ever
black president.
Hey, can he say
the word "ask"?
Or-or is that a word
we should avoid?
Yea, and I bet you I was the
voice of an animated bird.
(Joe's voice):
I thought I saw a cat.
I did see a cat.
Oh, my God,
look at that.
Wow, that looks
pretty bad.
Is the Chinese
guy dead?
(sniffs)
Wait.
We-we were in this car.
I can smell us all
in this car!
This must be the accident
that put us all
in the hospital.
See if there's a registration
in the glove compartment.
"Peter Griffin."
One of us is Peter Griffin.
Look at this indent
on the steering wheel.
It's a perfect match.
Oh, my God!
You're Peter Griffin!
Yeah, I am.
And you live
at 31 Spooner Street.
Finally, a real clue.
Let's go!
Wow, I own a house!
I just hope it doesn't have
one of those mailboxes
that looks like a cow.
I just want to seem cool to
these guys, but I really hope
I have one of those mailboxes
that looks like a cow.
"Moo," says my mailbox.
Well, this is
31 Spooner Street.
I'm home.
All right,
see you guys.
I'm gonna go shove my
hand down my pants
and see if that
goes someplace.
Guys! Guys!
It goes someplace!
(sniffs)
Hang on, I got something.
(sniffing)
I poop a lot on this lawn.
This must be where I live!
Hey, Shirt Pants,
come in here.
Oh, my God!
I know, I know!
You're my owner!
I knew it!
I knew we were pals!
Yeah, I mean, there's
no pictures of me,
but I see you've got a
dog collar and a leash.
And look how big
your doggie cage is.
You could fit
a human in there.
Clearly, you're
a good owner.
It's such a
weird situation.
I-I just think somebody
should be writing about it.
Yeah.
Do you... do you think
it should be me?
S-Should I be the one
writing about this?
Uh, I don't know.
I-I think it
should be me.
Then just do it, stop talking
about it for God's sake.
Oh, hey, guys.
Well, we got it
all figured out.
Turns out my name
is Glenn Quagmire,
and this is my dog.
JOE:
Hey, you guys!
Hey, I found my house.
Turns out my name's
Joe Swanson,
and I found this
police uniform in my closet.
Do you know
what that means?
I'm a stripper!
Well, it's good
we found out who we all are,
but we still
haven't found out
what the hell happened
to everybody else.
Yeah, I've been
thinking about that,
and I think the
best course of action
is for us to just go ahead and
start repopulating the Earth.
But there are no women.
Well, let's try
some stuff.
Hey, you guys want to
see something cool?
There's a bedroom upstairs
that belonged to some girl,
and she's got bras in there,
and the cups are
different sizes.
L-Like one of them's
a martini glass
and the other one's
some kinda melon.
Guys, you know how
we were thinking
that something must have
caused this situation...
or someone?
Yeah?
Look at that.
Oh, my God.
It's him.
He did this.
What do we do?
Check it out.
I got the little
freak's bra.
I'm gonna put it on.
Huh, this actually
fits pretty well.
Oh, wait, there's
a name on it.
It's mine.
My God.
Peter is responsible for
killing everyone on Earth.
But how could a guy like that
cause all this destruction?
Well, he's clearly
not just a guy.
He's some kind of
omnipotent alien,
with powers we can
only guess at.
Look at him--
watching, learning...
absorbing.
This janitor's in love
with this redheaded ashtray.
But why didn't
he kill us?
I don't know, maybe...
maybe he needs us.
Maybe we're important.
I mean, I do have all these
profound ideas and thoughts.
Maybe I was a deep
thinker of some kind.
Deep thinker?
I spent the whole morning
trying to teach you
one simple thing.
Give me paw.
Paw?
Good.
Other paw.
No. Other paw.
No!
We practiced this!
You're gonna make me look bad
in front of the other guys.
Other paw!
Finally!
You know, this
actually reminds me
of a quote by Milton...
Shut the (bleep) up.
Well, what are we gonna do?
What are we
gonna do about what?
(all gasp)
Oh, about the...
The, uh, th-th-the pie!
The pie we're all
gonna make for you for...
being such a great guy.
Aw, my God,
that sounds awesome.
I would kill everyone
in the world
and leave three survivors
for a piece of pie right now.
(nervous laughing)
Guys, really, what
are we gonna do?
Well, it seems obvious.
We gotta find a way
to kill him before he kills us.
Kill him?
How about we just get
the hell out of here?
Are you kidding me?
He'd catch us.
If this guy's an alien,
I bet he can fly.
He can probably
hear us right now.
He's probably got a laser beam
that can shoot us
through the walls.
(screaming)
He can't hit us
if we keep moving!
Can you... Can you not...
Can you...
I just took a bunch of
random stuff I found
in my medicine cabinet,
and you're really
freaking me out
right now.
Okay, maybe he doesn't
have a laser.
But listen, if we're gonna kill
him, we gotta find some guns.
Okay, well, let's go.
Not all of us. Somebody's
gotta go over there
and keep an eye on him, make
sure he doesn't go anywhere.
Oh, come on.
Why me?
'Cause I'm your owner
and I said so.
But I don't want to.
All right, then,
you asked for it!
What, what is that?
I found it
in my night table.
I thought it was a dog whistle,
but now I'm thinking
it's something you jam in your
urethra to make you last longer.
Man, I wonder if I'm one
of those secret assassins
who doesn't even know it,
but I'm a highly trained
killing machine.
Well, I could test that
by attacking you.
If you repel my attack,
maybe that means
you're a secret assassin.
Good idea.
I don't, I don't think
I'm a secret assassin.
(knocking)
Hey, uh...
knock, knock,
a-anybody home?
Oh, hey, buddy.
Come on in,
I could use some company.
Um, okay.
Hey, I know we're the only
people on Earth and all,
but what's with
all these Mexicans
coming here
to steal our jobs?
Hey, what are you
doin' down there?
Come on, sit up on
the couch with me.
Are you sure?
Mr. Quagmire says dogs aren't
allowed on the furniture.
I don't care
about that stuff.
Besides, you look like
you got a clean bum.
It is pretty clean.
I just cleaned it.
Ha. Bums are funny.
(chuckles)
They are kinda funny.
We all got one.
We all got one!
I was just gonna say that!
Isn't-isn't that weird?
(chuckles)
Everybody's got a bum!
(both laughing)
Mine's even got a secret
compartment in it
where you can store stuff.
Hey, you want a pretzel?
I'm okay.
You know, you ever think
if we could all just
spend more time celebrating our
similarities instead of just
standing on our differences,
the universe
would be a much better place?
Not really.
But that bum thing,
you're-you're on
to something there.
Y-You're, uh...
you're some kind of deep
thinker, aren't you?
(tires screech)
Where you goin'?
I-I think your...
your pie might be
about ready.
Hey, we're gonna share
that pie, buddy,
'cause, you know,
there's no "I" in "pie."
Except for the "I."
But enough about
numbers. You go.
So, we ready
to do this?
You guys, I'm
not sure that
Peter's the guy
we think he is.
He seems harmless and
actually kinda nice.
Oh, my God.
You slept with him!
What? No, no.
We were just watching TV,
but listen,
you've got to believe me, he's
not capable of hurting anyone.
Clearly he's
controlling your mind
with his superior
alien brain.
PETER: Ah, don't let 'em get
you down, Paul Blart.
Your life has dignity.
(laughs)
And comedy!
Oh, heavens!
Look, there's pretty solid
evidence that this guy
is responsible
for the elimination of
the entire human race,
and we need to take him out.
Okay, okay, you're right.
But he trusts me, so
you guys wait here,
and I'll go lure him out.
I have a lot of
dirty stuff in my house.
Wait, what the
hell's he doing?
He's supposed to be
luring Peter out here.
He's not doing
anything like that.
He's warning him!
They think I'm an alien?!
Yes, and you have to get
out of here right away!
But you're-you're
Quagmire's dog.
Why would you be
helping me instead of him?
Because...
I-I don't...
I don't know why.
I-I can't explain it.
I-I just...
I feel like
you're my friend.
(sighs)
You wouldn't understand.
No, I think I kinda do.
Come on, buddy.
Let's go!
I knew I couldn't trust you,
you filthy mongrel.
Guys, he didn't
do it, I swear.
Get out of the way, dog.
(shouts)
Please! I didn't do anything!
When you've been a stripper
as long as I have,
you know when you've
met a bad egg.
And you're a bad egg.
No! You bastards!
(sobbing)
(screams)
(beeping)
What the hell...
What's going on?
Stewie?
Well, Brian,
you proved me wrong.
What the hell
are you talking about?
What, what is all this?
You see, Brian, I conducted
a little experiment.
Remember our
little argument about
whether you and Peter
were actually friends?
Well, I wanted to prove
to you that I was right,
that your friendship was purely
a result of circumstance.
So I created a scenario in which
everyone's memories were erased,
to demonstrate
that you and Peter
would never naturally
associate with one another.
But I was wrong.
It appears you two have
a genuine bond after all.
Wow.
So we really were meant
to be friends.
I guess you were, yes.
So, are they gonna
remember any of this?
No, I'll wipe out
their whole day.
It'll be like
it never happened.
Wow.
Hey, what's going
on over there?
Oh, I wanted to see how
three women would react
in the same situation.
(arguing and screaming)
Stop it!
Ow! Ow!
Let go! Let go!
They've only been in there
for three minutes.
Haven't even tried to figure
out each other's names yet.
Thank you for watching "Family Guy" on
www.FOX-fan.ru